ظآزThe breeze of the 1990s drifts byظآز
ظآزMemories slowly flicker pastظآز
ظآزMy heartbeat
rises and falls with the tuneظآز
ظآزThe story quietly begins hereظآز
ظآزUnder the dim lights, our eyes meetظآز
ظآزTime seems to stand stillظآز
ظآزYour smile
breaks through the clouds like sunظآز
ظآزMelting the snow deep in my heartظآز
ظآزStreet posters spread signals of loveظآز
ظآزOur story slowly begins to fermentظآز
ظآزHand in hand,
going through every dusk cornerظآز
ظآزThe taste of happiness is so subtleظآز
ظآزCrossing back to the 1990s stageظآز
ظآزYou're my most beautiful surpriseظآز
ظآزLove's flame burns within my heartظآز
ظآزNot afraid of obstacles aheadظآز
ظآزSway with the rhythm.
Feel your heart poundظآز
ظآزThis love will never changeظآز
ظآزWe hold tight in this crazy eraظآز
ظآز1990s love is what we rely onظآز
=Once More Love in 1995=
=Episode 20=
Who exactly are you?
I'm your karma!
The mother is kind and beautiful.
She never hurt anyone,
but she was abandoned by her family,
betrayed by her friends,
and deceived by her lover.
They ganged up together
and ruined her entire family.
She left this world with regret.
But one day,
a miracle happened.
The daughter returned
to before her mother died.
She swore to eliminate every danger
and villain around her mother,
reversing her tragic life at its root.
Boss.
Are you okay?
Li.
Do you believe in time travel?
Time travel?
What's that?
(Zhuang Yan.)
(If what you said is true,)
(then why do you resist me so much?)
(Did I)
(hurt you in the future?)
Yan.
Is something on your mind?
You look troubled.
No.
Are you thinking about Qin then?
How could I be thinking about him?
Yan.
I can tell that Qin likes you.
You're clearly a perfect match,
so why do you keep avoiding him?
You keep saying you have no future,
but you've never been there.
How do you know you don't?
What if I say I've been there?
What do you mean?
Anyway,
our future together won't be good.
I don't want to go through that.
Forget it.
Let's go out and have some fun.
Sure.
Jerk.
Hey, sweetie.
All alone?
Get lost.
Have a drink with me.
Get lost!
Who hit me?
Is it that easy to be a thug in the 90s?
All you do is harass women.
Fine, you're lucky today.
You came out and drank alone
at this hour.
Did you learn your lesson?
None of your business.
I'll drink with you.
Then I'll drink too.
ظآزRaindrops tapping on the office windowsظآز
ظآزWorking overtime until late at night,
the coffee has turned coldظآز
ظآزThe fax machine
suddenly printed out a line of textظآز
ظآزFingers hoverظآز
ظآزMy heart skipped a beat
for three kilometersظآز
ظآزBetween the blindsظآز
ظآزI caught a glimpse
of your smiling eyesظآز
You two are really pathetic.
Throwing away your lives for a scumbag.
One day I'll take you out
to open your eyes.
I know a club.
Zhuang Yan.
Sure, I'll go then.
But are they as handsome as my brother?
Way more handsome than him.
I don't believe it.
Then don't come.
I'll take Shanshan instead.
Those abs and that build.
They're basically human bullfrogs.
Really?
Hey.
Slow down, you three.
What's wrong?
About the raw materials,
this wouldn't have happened
if I hadn't been used by Zhou Zeyang.
Even indirectly,
I seriously harmed the company.
According to the rules, I should resign.
If you make a mistake,
you take responsibility.
Tell accounting yourself tomorrow.
Your entire salary this month
is deducted.
Huh?
This raw material issue
was indeed caused by you.
But since it wasn't intentional,
as your superior,
I'm willing to give you
a chance to make amends.
Why did you say earlier
that you don't acknowledge me
as your sister anymore?
As your brother,
I'm glad you're home.
Long.
I want to kill you right now.
Long, calm down.
- Calm down.
- I can't calm down.
Give me some time, okay?
I'll get the money for you, Long.
Do you take me for an idiot?
I know
the palm oil money is with you.
Long.
I'll give you two choices.
Either...
Either you give me the money,
or I'll kill you today.
Long.
Let's talk this through.
I'll get the money now.
Hurry up.
I'll get the money.
I'll go get it. The money's inside.
Zhou Zeyang.
Zhang Guolong.
Give my money back.
Give my money back!
Police.
Freeze, don't move.
You knew I'd come and set me up?
Jerk.
Jerk, I'll kill you!
(Jinxin Food Co. Ltd)
Let go of me!
Jiamin.
Jiamin, I have nowhere to go now.
Qin Mo sued me.
All my bank cards are frozen.
Help me one last time.
Let's forget everything from before, okay?
Jiamin, listen to me.
I've contacted the media
to expose
Jinxin's additives exceeding limits.
You just need to help me
tamper with the food additives,
and I can make a comeback.
Then you'll still be
the company's only lady boss.
Food safety is Jinxin's bottom line.
I won't help you do evil again.
Zhou Zeyang.
Please take your CEO fantasy
and get as far away as possible.
Don't show up in front of me again!
You're cutting off my way out?
Then we'll die together.
Zhou Zeyang.
You've been using me all along.
You never loved me, did you?
This isn't using you.
The most important thing
for a person is value.
I'm helping you realize your value.
I've been blind
to hurt my brother and Shanshan for you.
I also almost destroyed Jinxin.
Enough talk.
Will you help or not?
No.
What are you doing?
Qin Mo.
Zhuang Yan.
Since you won't let me live in peace,
then none of us will live.
ظآزThe old dial tone circles in my earظآز
ظآزFaded tickets point to a cicada summerظآز
ظآزThe videotape
whispers your image in the frameظآز
ظآزAgainst the light, the plaid shirt
reveals a clear and transparent smileظآز
ظآزI'm a clumsy guest in a frozen sceneظآز
ظآزHow do I answer familiar lines?ظآز
ظآزI know
the train will leave this stationظآز
ظآزI know the ending's in a faded futureظآز
ظآزYet I want to approach that warmthظآز
ظآزEven one second rewrites missed linesظآز
ظآزRewind to 1995,
back to the street we metظآز
ظآزWind blows through the sycamore leaves
and lands on your shoulderظآز
ظآزI wish I could pause and stop timeظآز
ظآزLet unspoken love
be preserved forever as amberظآز
ظآزRewind to 1995,
gentle touch of fingertipsظآز
ظآزStar sparks in your eyes burn my chestظآز
ظآزThis looping script
is beyond my savingظآز
ظآزI can only stay with you till the end
in this inverted hourglassظآز